本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
嘿  Charlie  这是你姐姐Teddy在录视频日记
Hi, Charlie. it's your big sister Teddy with my video diary.
今天  我要和你聊聊关于好朋友的话题
So today, I want to talk to you about best friends.
你又在夸耀我了吧
You bragging about me again?
噢  这是Ivy  她是我的最好的朋友
Huh. yeah, this is Ivy. she's my BFF.
我还是她的英雄
I'm also her hero,
她是锅来我是盖  她是风儿我是沙
The wind beneath her wings, the hip in her hop,
她是绿叶我是花
The peanut to her butter.
- 我就是  - 那张说个没完的嘴
- I am-- - the mouth that wouldn't shut.
瞧瞧我们看上去如何
Let's see how we're looking.
很完美
Perfect!
- 我都想同咱俩约会  - 我都想同咱俩结婚
- I'd date us. - I'd marry us.
好吧  有什么重大新闻吗
So what's the big news?
你绝对不敢相信我为你做了什么
you are not gonna believe what I did for you
我看到了一个超帅的男孩在商场的美食广场工作
I saw the cutest guy working at the mall food court
为了戏剧效果  我们暂停一下
And pause for dramatic effect
明天我要过去跟他搭讪
Tomorrow I'm going to talk to him.
这算哪门子你为我做的事
How is this something you're doing for me?
也许他还有朋友啊  可爱的人总会有朋友的
Maybe he has a friend. the cute ones always have a friend.
就像  我有你  对吧
I mean, I have you, right?
嘿  姑娘们  忙什么呢
Hi, girls. What you doing?
没什么
Nothin'.
- 最近好吗  Ivy  - 很好
- How's it going, Ivy? - Real good.
别理她  她就会走开的
Ignore her. she'll go away.
你们这些孩子总是在玩手机
You girls are always on those phones.
- 你在和谁发短信呢  - 没和谁发
- Who are you texting now? - Nobody.
真希望我也会发短信
I wish I could do that.
嘿  那样的话  你和我就能互相发短信了  那样岂不是很好玩
Hey, then you and I could text each other. Wouldn't that be fun?
哦  天呐  妈妈  那样就太棒了
Oh my gosh, mom, I'd love that!
才怪
Eww!
- 但是我学不会怎么发短信  - 哦  那就没办法啦
- I don't think I can text from this phone. - oh, well.
你肯定能学会的  Duncan女士  你手机号多少
Sure you can, Miss D. what's your number?
555-0134
555-0134.
别理她啊
Not ignoring.
什么声音
What is that noise?
我刚给你发了条短信
I just sent you a text.
按一下这个键就可以看了
Just hit that button to read it.
哦  快看啊
Well, look at that.
哦  果然很好玩  Ivy
Oh, that's funny, Ivy.
那你就该回复个"lol"
Then your response is "lol."
就是“放声大笑”
"laugh out loud."
不是  不是的  不是让你笑出声来  而是把它打出来
No-- no, mom. you don't do it, you type it.
如果你想更俏皮点的话
Or if you want to get a little saucy,
你可以眨下眼
You can wink.
不是真眨  是打出来
Not there. There.
就是打一个分号和括号
Just a semicolon and parentheses.
哦  看起来确实像在眨眼睛
Oh, that does look like a wink.
真不敢相信我也会发短信了
I can't believe I'm finally a texter.
来看看我从厨房发短信你们能不能收到
Let's see if it works from the kitchen!
- "WHYD"  - 看你干的好事
- "WHYD"? - What have you done?
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
Today's all burnt toast
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
Running late,and dad jokes
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
Has anybody seen my left shoe
我闭上双眼  咬口早餐
I close my eyes, take a bite
■
翻译： Aaron
跳上车子  放声大笑
Grab a ride, laugh out loud
就在这里  我们的家
There it is up on the roof
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
I've been there, I've survived
所以请听取我的建议
So just take my advice
宝贝  不要放弃  世界有很多疯狂无奈
Hang in there, baby, things are crazy
■
校订： Edenwish  WaitinZ  love0forever
可是我知道你会有美好未来
But I know your future is bright
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, Baby
■
后期： WaitinZ  love0forever
不要怀疑
There is no maybe
一切终会如你所愿
Eveything turns out all right
生活有悲有喜
Sure life is up and down
可是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
But trust me, it comes back all around
你会喜欢将来的你
You're gonna love who you turn out to be
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, Baby
查莉成长日记  第一季第三集
Good Luck Charlie  S01E03  The Curious Case of Mr. Dabney
耶
Yeah!
自从你学会鼓掌后  这就比以前好玩多了
Yeah, this is way more fun since you've learned how to clap.
别装作没听见
Don't ignore me!
每次我跟你说去做什么事的时候  我希望你真的去做
When I tell you to do something, I expect you to do it!
少啰嗦  老女人
Get off my back, woman!
你想我少啰嗦吗  我求之不得呢
You want me off your back? I can arrange that.
Charlie  他们是我们的邻居  Dabney一家
Charlie, those are our neighbors, the Dabneys.
他们已经结婚很久很久了
They've been married a long time.
嘿  PJ  我刚把橄榄球踢进Dabney家的后院了
Hey, PJ, I just kicked the football into the Dabneys' backyard.
你能去把它拿回来嘛
Will you go get it?
没门  他们又得发飙了
No way! they're going at it again.
- 那橄榄球怎么办  - 谁在乎啊
- Well, what about the football? - Who cares?
它已经没了  和它告别吧
It's gone. Kiss it goodbye.
好吧  我很高兴你这么说
Well, I'm glad to hear you say that
因为那是你的橄榄球
Because it was your football.
哈  我早警告过你的
Ha! I warned you!
这就是你当恶丈夫的下场
That's what you get for being a bad husband!
现在你终于死了
And now you're dead!
外面有人吗
Is somebody out here?
谁在外面
Who's out here?
- 橄榄球呢  - 别提橄榄球了
- Where's the football? - Forget the football!
Dabney太太刚把Dabney先生谋杀了
Mrs Dabney just murdered Mr Dabney!
什么
What?!
我听到了她和他的尸体说话
I heard her talking to his corpse.
吓死我了
It was chilling.
你直说我就能明白  橄榄球你没拿回来  对吗
Just so I'm clear, you didn't get the football?
- 我是认真的  Gabe  - 拜托
- I'm serious, Gabe. - Come on.
Dabney太太也许是个小气  恶毒  残忍
Mrs Dabney may be a mean, vicious, cruel,
可怕  讨厌的老巫婆
horrible, nasty old witch,
但是她不可能干出这种事的
But she'd never do something like that.
- 你不相信我吗  - 不信
- You don't believe me? - No.
好吧  好吧  我会证明给你看的
Fine. fine, I'll prove it.
过来  Gabe
Come here, Gabe.
喂
Hello?
Dabney先生在家吗
Is Mr Dabney home?
他 现在接不了电话
He... can't come to the phone.
奇怪了
Interesting.
你是谁
Who is this?
呃  我算是个推销员吧
Uh-- I'm some sort of salesman.
Gabe  是你吗
Gabe, is that you?
你为什么认为我叫Gabe
Why would you assume my name is gabe?
因为我有来电显示
Because I have caller ID.
哦  是的  我是Gabe
Oh. then yeah, it's Gabe.
嘿
Hey!
哇  她在重压之下还是很冷静啊  起码我能确认这一点
Whoo! She's cool under pressure, I'll give her that.
- PJ  她不是凶手  - 我听得很清楚  Gabe
- PJ, she's not a murderer. - I heard what I heard, gabe.
你为什么不肯相信我
Why don't you believe me?
因为这是你说的啊  而你总是把事情搞错
Because you're you and you get things wrong.
你什么意思  觉得我是白痴吗
What are you saying, that I'm dumb?
呃  不是
Well, no.
你只是不怎么
You're just not very...
- 动脑筋  - 动脑筋
- thinky. - thinky?
Gabe  你为什么这么说
Gabe, why would you say something like that?
因为妈妈不许我叫你白痴
'cause mom said I can't call you dumb.
太悲剧了
It is so pathetic.
我妈妈居然在厨房发短信呢
My mom's in the kitchen texting away.
天呐  和她聊短信的那个人可有得受了
Gosh, I'd hate to be on the other end of that conversation.
你在和谁发短信呢
Who are you texting?
- 你妈妈  - 我很抱歉
- Your mom. - I am so sorry.
听着  我保证会让她不再烦你的
Look, I promise I'll get her out of your hair.
不  没事的  你妈妈挺酷的
No, it's okay. Your mom's cool.
我妈妈挺什么
My mom is what?
而且她真的很风趣
And she's really funny.
我妈妈很什么
My mom is what?
等下  她又发短信来了
Wait, that's her again.
你在和我妈妈聊什么呢
What are you talking about with my mom?
- 没什么  - 没什么
- Nothing. - Nothing?!
从来都是我们这么敷衍她的
That's what we say to her!
等下  我得回个"lol"给她
Hold on, I have to "lol" her.
好吧  看来"lol"已经失去它的意义了
Okay, well "lol" has officially lost all meaning.
我很抱歉  你有什么不满的吗
I'm sorry. is this a problem for you?
不  我只是觉得这样有点不太合适
No, I just think it's a little bit inappropriate.
不太合适  你现在说话的口气跟我妈妈一样了
Inappropriate? Now you sound like my mother.
是吗  你怎么知道你妈妈口气是什么样的
Well, how would you know what your mother sounds like?
你都花了这么多时间和我妈妈泡在一起了
You've been spending so much time with mine!
你有什么别扭的啊
What are you getting so whacked about?
你又不愿意跟她发短信
You didn't want to text her.
没错  那是因为她是我妈妈  不是我朋友
Well yeah, that's because she's my mom, not my friend.
如果我给你妈妈发短信你就不觉得很怪异吗
Wouldn't you be weirded out if I was texting your mom?
会啊  因为她都没有手机
Yes. Because she doesn't have a cell phone.
听着  T  如果不喜欢这样
Look, T, if you're not cool with this,
我就不再发了
I'll just stop.
不用  我才不在乎呢  我是说  这是个自由国家
No no, I don't care. I mean, it's a free country.
继续疯吧  给我妈妈发短信
Go crazy-- text my mom,
给我爸爸发即时消息  和我姑姑Helen视频聊天
IM my dad, video-chat my aunt Helen.
哦  说起你的姑姑Helen
Ooh! your aunt Helen?
你妈妈说她超炫
Your mom says she is da bomb diggitty!
我妈妈真的说了“超炫”吗
My mom really said "da bomb diggitty"?
那个  也可能是我自己加上的吧
Well, I may have added that part.
PJ  你不能再看那些悬疑推理电影了
PJ, you've got to stop watching these mysteries.
在没找到抓住Dabney太太的方法之前我是不会罢休的
Not until i figure out how to catch Mrs Dabney.
这些老电影会教我怎么破案的
These old movies are gonna help me do that.
这就好比说动画片能教你穿墙术
That's like saying cartoons will teach you how to run through walls.
我吃过苦头知道那行不通
Learned that the hard way.
妈妈  你能去开门吗
Mom! Can you get that?!
没问题  我来开了  我比你离门近多了
Sure, I'll get the door. I am a lot closer to it.
你好  Dabney夫人
Hello, Mrs. dabney.
- 你好  - 请进吧
- Hello. - Come on in.
小心  杀人犯来家里了
Heads up! killer in the house.
他们这次又闯什么祸了
What have they done this time?
就这一次  据我所知  还没闯祸
For once, nothing-- that I know of.
我也很高兴见到你
It's nice to see you too.
我想和你丈夫说点事  谢谢
I'd like to speak with your husband, please.
我这就告诉他你来找他了
I'll let him know you're here.
我现在开始用短信了
I'm a texter now.
我正给他发短信呢
I'm texting.
真是事半功倍啊
Really speeds things up.
今天谁丢球了吗
Somebody lose a ball today?
也许吧  你今天失去什么了吗  Dabney夫人
Possibly. Did you lose anything today, Mrs Dabney?
亲爱的  这什么意思 “有人在doof”
Honey, what does this mean  "somebody's at the doof."
我的老天
OMG!
我是想说在门口的
I meant "door"!
等会再和你说
TTYL.
(Talk to you later)
有什么事吗  Dabney夫人
What can I do for you, Mrs Dabney?
- 你是专门杀虫的是吗  - 我是害虫防治专家
- You're an exterminator, right? - pest control specialist.
也许你可以帮我解决这个问题
Maybe you can help me with a problem I'm having.
我该怎么除去家里那股死尸的味道
How do I get the smell of death out of my house?
你能把电视声音关小点吗
Will you turn that TV down?
那么你觉得你家里有什么东西死了吗
So you think something died in your house?
哦  我知道有东西死了
Oh, I know something is dead
好吧  你首先要做的就是
Well, first thing you're gonna have to do
找到尸体然后丢掉
is locate and dispose of the carcass.
我想这事你可以让Dabney先生去做
I suppose you could get Mr Dabney to do that.
哦  Dabney先生得有段时间不能做家务了
Oh, Mr Dabney won't be doing anything around the house for a while--
得有很长一段时间  他 走了
A long while. he's... gone.
知道吗  你们不如把电视关掉算了
You know what, would you just turn it off?
你的儿子们今天中什么邪了
What's wrong with your boys today?
我才刚看到他们
I just got here.
呃  好吧  教你个干我们这行的老办法
Um, all right, old trick of the trade
你找些枫树糖浆  放在灶上
Get yourself some maple syrup, put it on the stove,
慢慢炖  这样就能除掉那个味道
Let it simmer-- that should get rid of the smell.
谢了  你的建议对我帮助不小
Thank you. That's very useful information.
再见了  孩子们
Bye, boys.
"ITBOOTP"
这又是什么意思
What does that stand for?
卫生间没有手纸了
In the bathroom out of toilet paper!
不用说这么具体
TMI!
(Too Much Information)
真是不敢相信  你真的说对了
I can't believe it, but you were right!
Dabney夫人真的杀人了
Mrs Dabney did it.
哇  说对事的感觉原来是这样的啊
Wow! this is what it feels like to be right, huh?
我喜欢这感觉
I like it!
真可惜有人死了  不过
Too bad somebody had to die, but--
- 你现在打算怎么办  - 我必须得告诉爸爸妈妈
- What are we gonna do now? - I have to tell mom and dad!
他们不会相信你的
They're never gonna believe you.
我才十岁我都不肯信你
I didn't believe you and I'm 10.
那我们要找证据了
Well, then we need proof.
而且我必须要警告你  Gabe  在我们找到证据之前
And I have to warn you, Gabe, until we get that proof,
我们生命只怕还处于危险之中
Our lives may be in danger.
我以为我们已经把电视关了呢
I thought we turned that off.
第九个题你怎么答的
What'd you get for number nine?
瑞士
Switzerland.
是吗  这个答案很奇怪  因为我们是在做数学
Well, that's odd since we're doing math.
- 嗨  - 嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
妈  你来这儿干吗
Mom, what are you doing here?
才五点  还不到你接我的时候啊
You weren't supposed to pick me up at five.
Teddy给我留言让我早点来
Teddy left a message and said to come by early
有些关于“放松”的事
Something about "chilling"?
是的  没错
Yeah, that's right.
我想你妈妈和我可以一起放松一会儿
Thought your mom and I could chill for a little while.
是吗  这就是你的打算吗
Really? This is what you're doing?
是的  这就是我们的打算
Yeah well, this is what we're doing,
如果你不介意的话
So if you will excuse us,
- 我们两个想单独聊聊  - 当然不介意  你们聊吧
- We'd like a little privacy please. - Sure. fine.
我会去厨房  和你妈妈聊聊
I'll be in the kitchen with your mom.
坐这儿来
Come on over.
坐我旁边  闺蜜
Sit down next to me, girlfriend.
这是怎么回事啊  Ivy惹麻烦了吗
What's this all about? Is ivy in trouble?
哦  不是的
Oh, no.
她是不是又吃巧克力上瘾了
Is she back on the chocolate?
不是  不是  不是的  Ivy没事
No no no, Ivy's fine.
我只是想花点时间和一位很酷的妈妈一起玩会儿
I just wanted to spend some time with one of the cool moms.
- 就是你  - 哦
- You. - Oh.
好吧
Okay.
你喜欢你的外套  你在哪儿弄的
I love your outfit. Where'd you get it?
我的衣橱
My closet.
你真风趣啊  我敢赌很多人都这么说你吧  对吧
You are so funny. I bet you get that a lot, right?
- 没有 - 没有吗
- No. - no?
我们放松完了吗
Are we done chilling?
是的  结束了  现在该是派对时间了
Yes. yes, we are. Because it is time to par-tay.
让我们舞动起来吧
Let's get jam started.
耶  来吧  W女士  疯狂一下
Yeah! come on, Miss W! Let your freak flag fly!
耶
Yeah!
这个有点吵  你能关小点儿声吗
That's kind of loud. Could you lower that, please?
好的
Yeah.
再关小点儿
A little bit more.
好了
Perfect.
呃  嘿  你想玩点好玩的吗
Uh, hey, want to do something fun?
我喜欢给我妹妹拍视频日记
I like making these video diaries for my baby sister.
我们一起给她打个招呼吧
So how about we say hi?
你好  Charlie  这里是Teddy
Hi, Charlie. it's teddy here
以及我的新朋友Wentz夫人
With my new friend Mrs wentz.
你好
Hello.
让我们看看效果怎么样
Let's see how we look.
哦  我都想同咱俩约会  你说呢
Ooh, I'd date us. Wouldn't you?
我都结婚了
I'm married.
好吧  视频到此为止吧
Okay, that's enough of that.
知道吗  我们一直在玩我喜欢玩的东西
Now, you know what? We've been doing a lot of my fun stuff.
跟我聊聊你自己吧  你平时都喜欢玩些什么
Tell me-- tell me about you. what do you like to do for fun?
- 我喜欢织毛衣  - 哦
- I like to knit. - Ooh!
那个很酷啊  因为  因为  你还喜欢别的什么吗
That is so cool because... because... anything else?
- 我喜欢看书  - 哦  是吗  我也喜欢
- I like to read. - Oh, yeah? Me too.
你喜欢看什么书呢
What kind of stuff do you like to read?
针织杂志
Kniiting magazines
太炫了  我是说我们有这么多共同之处
That's awesome. I mean, we have so much in common.
你知道吗  我一看针织杂志
You know, once I start reading knitting magazines,
就是你从你包里抽出来的这种
Which you're pulling out of your bag.
好了  她走了
Okay, she's gone.
计划是这样的
Here's how this is gonna go down.
我先跳过这个篱笆  你再把Charlie递给我
I'm gonna jump over the fence, you hand Charlie to me.
- 然后  - 或者我直接从这个门进来
- And then-- - Or I could just walk through the gate
就像这样
Like this.
你知道这儿有个门吧
You did know there was a gate, right?
是的  我都骑在门上了怎么会不知道呢
Yes. would I be riding on top of it if I didn't?
现在怎么办
Now what?
现在我们该缉拿凶手归案了
Now it's time to be in operation "catch a killer"...
同时得照看宝宝
While babysitting.
那么  我们要找什么
So, what are we looking for?
证据  线索  还有凶器
Evidence, clues, a weapon.
要能找到Dabney先生的尸体也不错
Mr Dabney's rotting corpse would be nice.
哦  天呐  这也太可怕了
Oh my gosh, that's horrible!
- 什么东西  你看到什么了  - 那面墙的涂装颜色
- What? what do you see? - That paint color--
和这个房间太不融洽了
It's so wrong for that room!
- 我看了很多设计类的节目  - 集中注意力
- I watch a lot of design shows. - Focus!
- 快看  有东西在动  - 哪里
- Look. Something's moving. - Where?
沙发旁边  就在那儿
By the couch, right-- right there.
- 是个婴儿  - 是Charlie
- It's a baby! - It's Charlie!
不  怎么可能  Charlie就在
No, it's not. charlie's right over--
在发生杀人案的屋子里
inside the murder house!
好的  尽量跟上我
Okay, try to stay with me now
我们要来个有点难度的了
Because we're going to get a little wild.
不再是平织一针  反织两针
Instead of knit one, purl two,
我们提高到平织一针  然后反织三针
We kick it up to knit one, purl three!
那样合法吗
Is that even legal?
我不知道
I don't know,
但是我喜欢在危险中生活
But I just like living dangerously!
好吧  我去拿点饮料
Okay, I'm gonna go get something to drink.
- 你要喝什么吗  - 哦  暂时不用
- Do you want anything? - Oh, not now.
我现在进入状态了
I'm in the zone!
你来在这儿干吗
What you doing in here?
宣告放弃
Giving up.
她让你痛不欲生了吧
Did she suck the life out of you?
是的  差不多吧
Yeah, pretty much.
现在你知道我为什么老是泡在你家了吧
Now you see why I'm always at your house.
嗯  我很抱歉
Yeah, I'm so sorry.
在你和我妈妈的事上我太自私了
I was being selfish with my mom.
尽管我还是认为这有些怪异
And even though I think it's a little bit weird,
不过现在你想怎么给她发短信就怎么发吧
You can text her as much as you want.
我想到了个更好的主意
I think I got a better idea.
然后呢  记好了
And then, get this,
如果你打个分号和括号
If you type in a semicolon parentheses,
- 就会出现  - 眨眼的表情
- You get a-- - Winky face!
我得去买个手机了
I have got to get a cell phone.
我喜欢这个主意  你让我们的妈妈腻在一起
I like it. You put our moms together
这样她们就不会再来烦我们了  你真是天才
And they leave us alone. You are brilliant.
瞧  这就是为什么我们是最好的朋友
See, this is why we're BFFs.
我负责做个聪明人而你负责赏识我
I'm brilliant and you recognize it.
如果我打ROTF
Now if I type "ROTF."
那我是不是真的要在地上打滚
Do I actually have to roll on the floor?
我刚开始也这么想的
I thought the same thing at first,
但是不用
But no.
这玩意儿能把她吸引出来
This'll get her out.
Charlie喜欢叮当作响的东西
Charlie loves things that rattle.
好吧  Charlie  快来吧
Okay, girl. Charlie, come on.
过来拿钥匙  过来拿钥匙
Get the keys. Get the keys!
噢  老天  我把钥匙弄掉了
Aw, man! I dropped the keys.
这下好了
Fantastic!
现在我们连自己的家都回不了了
Now we can't get into our house either.
- 我看不到Charlie了  她去哪儿了  - 哦  她在那儿
- I don't see charlie. Where'd she go? - Oh, there she is.
等等  她把什么戴自己头上了
Wait, what is she putting on her head,
洗碗布吗
A dishtowel?
是Dabney夫人的内裤
Mrs Dabney's underpants!
噢
Oh!
- 天呐  - 噢
- Man! - Oh-ho!
快点  我们得把她从房里弄出来
Come on, we gotta get her out of there.
嗯  快来
Yeah, come on.
你们在我的院子里干嘛
What are you doing in my yard?
我们想过来帮你提东西
We're here to help you with your groceries.
你愿意帮忙吗
You want to be helpful?
我喜欢尝试新鲜事物
I like to try new things.
来  让我帮你提那个
Here, let me give you a hand with that.
这个我能自己搞定
I can handle the groceries.
但是既然你们来了
But as long as you're here,
你们可以进房里帮我做点别的事
I could use your help with something inside.
进房里  太好了
Inside? Perfect.
我先去把这些东西放下
Let me just put my groceries down.
- 慢慢来  - 就是就是
- Take your time. - Yeah. Yeah.
- Charlie在哪儿呢  - 呃
- Where's Charlie? - uh--
- 去窗帘后面找找  - 好的
- Look behind the curtains! - Okay.
- 不在这儿  - 她在那儿
- Nothing! - There she is!
哦  我找到你了
Oh, I've got you.
嗯
Yeah.
别扔给我
I don't want it!
别扔了
Stop it!
这个宝宝哪儿来的啊
Where did that baby come from?
Charlie吗  我一直都在抱着她啊
Charlie? I've been holding her the whole time.
- 是吗  - 真是遗憾  Dabney夫人
- You have? - That's sad, Mrs Dabney.
据说视力是最早开始衰退的
They say the eyes are the first things to go.
我们要走了
We gotta go.
别这么急着走  把孩子放下来
Not so fast. Put the baby down.
我需要你们帮我搬点东西
I need you to carry something out for me.
帮我把这个大衣箱搬到车里
I want you to take this trunk out to my car.
它太重了我搬不动
It's too heavy for me.
搬这个干什么  里面装着什么呢
Why? What's in it?
一些我早就该扔掉的东西
Something I should've gotten rid of a long time ago.
- 你要运到哪儿去  - 垃圾场
- Where are you taking it? - To the dump.
垃圾不就得扔到那儿去吗
That's where you take trash, isn't it?
垃圾
Trash?!
Dabney先生不是垃圾  他是人
Mr Dabney wasn't trash, he was a person!
你们在说什么呢
What are you talking about?
你很清楚我在说什么
You know exactly what I am talking about.
你谋杀了你丈夫  然后把他塞进了那个箱子
You bumped off your husband and stuffed him into that trunk.
- 你们是这么想的吗  - 我们知道正是如此
- Is that what you think?! - That's what we know!
她要干什么  哦  小心了
What is she-- oh, watch it!
她成了杀人狂魔了
She's kill-crazy!
你想看看箱子里是什么吗
You want to see what's in here?
自己过来看
Take a look.
哇  是Dabney先生
Whoa! It's Mr Dabney!
而且他都已经腐烂成骷髅了
And he's already decomposed!
那才不是Dabney先生
That's not Mr Dabney.
这是他上课用的骷髅标本
That's a skeleton he used in his classroom.
他以前是个教自然的老师
He used to be a science teacher.
可是我听到你冲她大喊大叫
But I heard you screaming at him.
你骂他是个坏丈夫  然后你又说
You called him a bad husband and then you said,
现在你终于死了
"and now you're dead!"
哦  你肯定是听到我和肥皂剧里的人自言自语了
Oh! you must have heard me talking back to someone on my soaps.
肥皂剧
Soaps?
肥皂剧  就是电视连续剧
Soap operas... on TV...
比如他们就该给你们拍部电视剧叫做
Like the one they should name after you two--
“年轻无知的人”
"the young and the clueless."
好吧  如果Dabney没死  那他在哪儿
Well, if Mr Dabney isn't dead, then where is he?
在他那个也许希望他死掉的妈妈那儿
At his mother's probably wishing he was dead.
那么  你怎么解释死尸的气味呢  你还专门去问过我爸呢
Well, then how do you explain the smell of death you asked my dad about?
有只死老鼠在我烘干机的管道里
Dead possum in my dryer vent.
那么  你怎么解释
Well, then how do you explain--
我觉得你已经解释得很明白了
That's pretty much it, I guess.
还有一个问题
Just one more question--
你有饼干吃吗
Do you have any cookies?
出去
Get out.
我的内裤在怎么会在壁炉里面
What are my underpants doing in the fireplace?
得走了
Gotta go!
哒哒哒  她来啦
Dat-da-da-da! Here she comes!
世上最酷的妈妈  耶
Coolest mom in the world! Yay.
好吧  这是干什么呢
Okay, what's all this?
哦  就是告诉Charlie我有多爱你
Oh, just showing Charlie how much I love you.
哦  我也爱你  宝贝
Oh, I love you too, sweetie.
我也爱你  Charlie
And I love you too, Charlie.
哦  妈妈  我一直在想
Oh, so mom, I've been thinking--
也许你我可以互相发短信
Maybe you and I should start texting.
我是说  你是个很酷的妈妈  对吧
I mean, you are a pretty cool mom, right?
哦  抱歉  宝贝  我已经不再发短信了
Oh, sorry, honey. Those days are over.
拇指发炎了
Text thumbs.
拇指发炎了  不愧是我们的妈妈
Text thumbs? That's our mom--
这么快就从酷妈妈变成丢人的妈妈了
From cool to embarrassing just like that.
好了  祝你好运  Charlie
All right. good luck, Charlie.
嘿  孩子们  最好去给你们的朋友做个三明治吃
Hey, guys. Better make your friend a sandwich.
他都瘦的皮包骨头了
He's looking a little thin.
你们从哪儿弄来的那玩意儿
Where'd you guys get that thing?
Dabney夫人准备扔掉来着
Mrs Dabney was throwing it out.
嗯  这是Dabney先生的东西  他以前是自然老师
Yeah, it belonged to Mr Dabney. He was a science teacher.
Dabney先生才不是自然老师  他是音乐老师
Mr dabney wasn't a science teacher. He was a music teacher.
什么
What?!
- 也就是说  - 这个是
- That means-- - This is--
Dabney先生才不是音乐老师
Mr Dabney wasn't a music teacher.
你把他和街对面的Dixon先生搞混了
You're thinking of-- of Mr Dixon across the street.
哦  没错  Dabney先生是当过自然老师
Oh, that's right. Mr Dabney was a science teacher.
你觉得孩子们是不是有点神经兮兮的啊
The boys seem a little jumpy to you?
啊  我才刚看到他们
Ah, I just got here.